Nature Conservancy in Arizona records, 1884-1999
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 1: The Nature Conservancy in Arizona, Chapter Materials, 1962-1999, 6.70 linear feet (approximately 13,400 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  - Series 5: Research and Reference, 1962-1996, 1.20 linear feet (approximately 2,400 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains six subseries: Federal Agencies (1975-1992), Maps and Aerial Images (1971-1992), News Clippings (1966-1979), Organizations and Institutions (1977-1996), Plans and Reports (1978-1994), and Subject files (1962-1992). Federal Agencies documents the materials produced by various federal agencies. Maps and Aerial Images includes maps and aerial images of sites and geographic areas of interest and the documentation and procedures for identifying and requesting these images. News Clippings documents various events and subjects of interest. Organizations and Institutions includes information produced by non-profit environmental and other organizations. Plans and Reports includes plans and reports generated by various state and federal government agencies, institutions, and The Nature Conservancy, national organization on various methods, ecological resources and areas of interest. Subject files include material arranged by topic.
    - Subseries 1: Federal Agencies, 1975-1992
      - Bureau of Land Management-News Releases, Updates, Legislation and Reports. 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 35-37)
      - Coronado National Forest-Site Wildlife and Habitat Data Sheets and News Clippings. 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Heritage Conservation and Recreation Service- Nationwide Rivers Inventory. 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - National Park Service-Brochure, National Park System in Arizona. undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Soil Conservation Service-General Information. 1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - U.S. Department of Interior and Watt, James-News Clippings and Press Release. 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service-Brochures and Federal Register. 1985-1992 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service-Southern Arizona Trip, Packet. 1992 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - U.S. Forest Service- "Alternative Goals: 1985 Resources Planning Act Program." 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - U.S. Forest Service-Environmental Impact Statements and Land and Resource Management Planning. 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Subseries 2: Maps and Aerial Images, 1971-1996
      - Aerial Image Research and Ordering Procedures. 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - Aerial Image Research and Ordering Procedures. 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
      - Maps and Notes. 1971-1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Microfiche-Mapline Plots of Sonora and Gila River. undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - U.S. Geological Survey Brochures. undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Subseries 3: News Clippings, 1966-1979
      - News Clippings.. 1966-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6-8)
    - Subseries 4: Organizations and Institutions, 1977-1996
      - The Keystone Center-Southwest Regional Meeting Information and Policy Report. 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
      - Laboratory of Ornithology at Cornell-Ornithology Brochures. undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Natural Areas Association-General Information.. undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Newsletters-Miscellaneous. 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Operation Stronghold Coalition-Brochure. undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - PRONATURA-Asociacion Mexicana Proconservacion de la Naturaleza. 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Save Our Public Lands (Sagebrush Rebellion)-Conference Information and Notes. 1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - School of Renewable Natural Resources, University of Arizona-Director's Advisory Council. 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Southwest Environmental Services-General Information Packet. 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - The Trust for Public Land-Annual Reports and News Updates. 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Tucson Botanical Gardens-Master Plan Workshop and Membership Roster. 1983 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Subseries 5: Plans and Reports, 1977-1994
      - "Comments on Draft Allotment Management Plan for the Santa Maria Community Allotment." 1990 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - "Evaluation of a Potential Black-Footed Ferret Reintroduction Site in the Aubrey Valley, Coconino County, Arizona Game and Fish Department." 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - "The Global 2000 Report to the President", Council on Environmental Quality and the State Department. 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - "In Quest of the Mystical '90%'." undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - "An Inventory of Natural Areas in the State of Arizona", Arizona State Parks, SCORP. 1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - "Mazatzal Wilderness Implementation Plan", Tonto National Forest, Forest Service, USDA. 1993 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - "Public Use of Earth and Space Science Data Over the Internet", Office of Arid Lands, University of Arizona. 1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - "Riparian Habitat and Instream Flow Studies: Lower Verde River, Fort McDowell Reservation." 1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - "Salt River Project Annual Report, 1981-1982." 1982 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - "Site Conservation Planning: Issues and Recommendations", The Nature Conservancy. 1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Status Report on Taxon: Lilaeopsis schaffneriana Subspecies recurva, U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service. 1991 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - "Unique Wildlife Systems of Arizona", U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service, Region 2. 1978 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - "U.S. Exports and Imports of Cacti, 1977-1979", International Convention Advisory Commission. 1981 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - "Upper Trout Creek Inventory." 1992 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Subseries 6: Subject Files, 1962-1992
      - Arizona Mobile Home Parks Residential Landlord and Tenant Act. 1991 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Ecotourism and Riparian Areas. 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Environmental Hazardous Waste. 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Environmental Site Assessments-Advanced Course, The Nature Conservancy. 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - Grazing Regulations. 1962-1971 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Hydrological Information. 1992 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Subgroup 2: Site Files, 1884-1997, 7.30 linear feet (approximately 14,600 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  The material in Subgroup 2 consists of the site files of the organization, which contain forty-two series arranged alphabetically by site name. Each series in this subgroup may include one or all of the following subseries: Administration, Correspondence, Ecology, History and Archaeology, Photographs and Images, and Protection and Management. The forty-two site file series include: Appleton-Whittell Research Ranch Sanctuary (1972-1996), Aravaipa Canyon Preserve (1949-1993), Arivaca Creek (1978-1989), Baboquivari Mountains Macrosite (1969-1984), Bill Williams River Megasite (1975-1994), Buenos Aires National Wildlife Refuge (1982-1992), Canelo Hills Cienega Preserve (1967-1993), Chiricahua Cave Creek Macrosite (1987), Chiricahua Portal Preserve (1988), Chiricahua Turkey Creek (1982), Coffeepot Mountain Macrosite (1977-1986), Eagle Creek Natural Area (1977-1986), Empire Ranch Megasite (1986), Escondido Falls (1986), Goodding RNA Extensions (1987), Guadalupe Canyon (1979-1982), Hartwell Canyon Preserve (1986-1989), Hassayampa River Preserve (1986-1994), Holbrook NE Site (1981), Jak Ranch (1988), Kino Springs (1978-1989), Kiper Springs (1979-1989), Leslie Spring (1986-1988), McDowell Mountains (1995), Muleshoe Ranch Cooperative Management Area (1884-1997), Oracle State Park (1973-1989), Patagonia-Sonoita Creek Preserve (1965-1993), Ramsey Canyon Preserve (1953-1993), Rio Yaqui Headwaters System (1983), Sabino Creek Macrosite (undated), San Bernardino Ranch Site (1979-1983), San Francisco Peaks Site (1988), San Pedro River Biopreserve (1973-1998), San Rafael Valley Macrosite (1980), Santa Rita Experimental Range ( 1987), Tavasci Marsh Site (1973-1993), Tumamoc Hill Site (1987-1990), Vekol Valley Special Management Area (1988), Volunteer Canyon-Smith Road Site (1988-1990), Waterman Mountains Site (1986-1988), White Canyon (1989), and Whitewater Draw (1991).
  - Series 1: Appleton-Whittell Research Ranch Sanctuary, 1972-1996, .05 linear feet (approximately 100 items) Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains one subseries: Protection and Management (1972-1996). Files include general information, a management plan and an annotated bibliography relevant to this site.
    - Subseries 1: Protection and Management, 1972-1996
      - General Information. 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Management Plan and Annotated Bibliography. 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Series 2: Aravaipa Canyon Preserve, 1949-1993, 1.10 linear feet (approximately 2,200 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains six subseries: Administration (1970-1993), Correspondence (1970-1975), Ecology (1950-1989), History and Archaeology (1953-1973), Photographs and Images (undated), and Protection and Management (1949-1990). Files document land purchases, general correspondence, ecological resources, prehistoric and historic land use, management, recreational use and stewardship of the preserve.
    - Subseries 1: Administration, 1970-1993
      - Fiscal-Expense Documentation. 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 43-46)
      - Land-Deed and Property Agreements. 1970 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Land-Painted Cave (Mulvania) Appraisal, Deed and Notes. 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Land-Property Valuations, Appeals and General Information. 1983-1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Land-Tax Notices and Property Valuations. 1982-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
      - Reports-Quarterly. 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1970-1975
      - General. 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
    - Subseries 3: Ecology, 1950-1989
      - Ecological Summary. 1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Ecological Summary-Holy Joe Ranch. 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Reports-Hydrological and Recommendations. 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
      - Reports-Fishes of Aravaipa and Aravaipa Watershed Area. 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Reports-Wildlife and Reconnaissance. 1950-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Subseries 4: History and Archaeology, 1953-1973
      - Archaeological Survey, Arizona State Museum. 1953-1959 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Report of Explorations from Pima Villages to Rio Grande and News Clippings. 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Subseries 5: Photographs and Images, undated
      - General. undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Subseries 6: Protection and Management, 1949-1990
      - Bureau of Land Management, Aravaipa Canyon Wilderness Bill and Plan. 1978-1990 (Box 8, Folder 18-20)
      - Defenders of Wildlife Trust. 1969-1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - General. 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 22-23)
      - Holy Joe Ranch-Project Summary. 1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Management Plan and Notes, Old. 1970-1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Management Policy and Land Use. 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 26-27)
      - Position Paper and Appeal Drafts. 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Preserve Proposal. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Recreation Activity Plan and Maps. 1949-1971 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Research References and Foundation Proposal Draft. 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Stewardship. 1970-1980 (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
      - Stewardship. 1981-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Series 3: Arivaca Creek, 1978-1989, .05 linear feet (approximately 100 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains one subseries: Protection and Management (1978-1989). Files document land acquisitions and management at this site.
    - Subseries 1: Protection and Management, 1978-1989
      - Cruce Ranch- Project Package and Tract Summary. 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Cruce Ranch-Property Summary and Project Acquisition Proposal. 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Honnas Tract-Project Package and Ecological Summary. 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Series 4: Baboquivari Mountains Macrosite, 1969-1984, .10 linear feet (approximately 200 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains three subseries: Administration (1978-1979), Ecology (1979-1983), and Protection and Management (1975-1989). Files document land acquisition, ecological resources, management and stewardship of the macrosite.
    - Subseries 1: Administration, 1978-1979
      - Land-Acquisition and Leases. 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Subseries 2: Ecology, 1979-1983
      - Thomas Canyon-Floral Survey and Bird Report. 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Subseries 3: Protection and Management, 1975-1989
      - Cumming Land and Livestock Corp. et al. Tract. 1969-1982 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
      - Stewardship. 1978-1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Thomas Canyon-Amsonia kearneyana. 1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Series 5: Bill Williams River Megasite, 1975-1994, .05 linear feet (approximately 100 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains three subseries: Administration (1978-1994), Ecology (1983), and Protection and Management (1975-1989). Files document the stewardship, ecological resources, and management of the megasite.
    - Subseries 1: Administration, 1978-1994
      - Stewardship. 1978-1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Subseries 2: Ecology, 1983
      - Reports-Wildlife. 1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Subseries 3: Protection and Management, 1975-1989
      - Project Acquisition Proposals, Arizona Ranch and Metals Company. 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Project Package. 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Series 6: Buenos Aires National Wildlife Refuge, 1982-1992, .05 linear feet (approximately 100 items). Arrangement: alphabetical
    . This series contains one subseries: Ecology (1982-1992). Files document the ecological resources of the refuge.
    - Subseries 1: Ecology, 1982-1992
      - Arizona Site Summary. 1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Reports-Plant Life and Masked Bobwhite Reintroduction. 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Series 7: Canelo Hills Cienega Preserve, 1967-1993, 1.30 linear feet (approximately 2,600 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains five subseries including: Administration (1967-1993), Correspondence (1969-1985), Ecology (1968-1987), Photographs and Images (1970-1975), and Protection and Management (1974-1991). Files document the fiscal administration, land purchases and additions, general correspondence, ecological resources, management and stewardship of the preserve.
    - Subseries 1: Administration, 1967-1993
      - Fiscal-Budget Information. 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Fiscal-Deficit Account. 1968-1981 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Fiscal-Expense Documentation. 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
      - Fiscal-Expense Documentation. 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
      - Fiscal-Expense Documentation. 1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Fiscal-Expense Documentation. 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Fiscal-Expense Documentation and Land Purchase. 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
      - Fiscal-Operating Revenues and Expenses. 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Fiscal-Tax Records. 1969-1982 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Land-Deeds, Mortgage and Insurance Documents. 1968-1984 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Land-Ewing Addition-Acreage Appraisal. 1983 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Land-Ewing Addition I- Deed, Option Agreement and Maps. 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Land-Ewing Addition I- Purchase and Project Acquisition Proposal. 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Land-Ewing Addition II-Land Deed and Purchase Documents, Water Rights and Project Acquisition Proposal. 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 33-35)
      - Land-Ewing Addition II-Project Acquisition Proposal and Land Purchase. 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Land-Ewing Addition III-Land Deed, Insurance Policy and Financial Management. 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 37-38)
      - Land-Ewing Addition III-Project Acquisition Proposal and Land Acquisition. 1983 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Land-Ewing Addition IV-Land Purchase and Option Agreements and Maps. 1972-1987 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Land-Ewing Addition IV-Project Summary (Tract). 1986 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Land-Ewing Addition IV-Right of First Refusal. 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Land-Ewing Addition V-Land Purchase Agreements and Stewardship Information. 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Land-Ewing Addition V-Project Summary. 1986 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Land-Ewing Addition VI-Land Purchase Agreements, Deed and Closing Package. 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Land-Ewing Addition VI-Maps and Conservation Easement. undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Land-Original Knipe Purchase. 1968-1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Reports-Annual, Quarterly and Stewardship. 1973-1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Stewardship. 1968-1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1969-1985
      - Ewing Addition I. 1971-1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - General. 1969-1979 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
      - General. 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Subseries 3: Ecology, 1968-1987
      - Ecological Summary. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Ecological Summary-Ewing Addition. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Handbook-Geology, Bird and Plant Lists, and Water Analysis. 1974-1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - "Preserve Summary-A Guidebook for Scientists and Educators", Arizona Academy of Science. 1968-1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Research Proposal and International Biological Program Survey. 1972-1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Subseries 4: Photographs and Images, 1970-1975
      - General. 1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
    - Subseries 5: Protection and Management, 1974-1991
      - Ewing Addition I-II-Project Acquisition Proposals and Maps. 1981 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Management Plan, Outline and Site Stewardship Summaries. 1983-1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Prescribed Burn Proposal, Plan and Report. 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Preserve Plans, Notes and Stewardship Summaries. 1974-1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Stewardship Summaries. 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Series 8: Chiricahua Cave Creek Macrosite, 1987, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains one subseries: Protection and Management (1987). The file documents the protection and management of the macrosite.
    - Subseries 1: Protection and Management, 1987
      - Project Package. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Series 9: Chiricahua Portal Preserve, 1988, undated, .025 linear feet (approximately 50 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains one subseries: Protection and Management (1988, undated). Files document the protection and management of three tracts of land on the preserve.
    - Subseries 1: Protection and Management 1988, undated
      - Project Package, Chew Tracts. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Project Package, Spofford Tract. undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Project Package, Steele Tract. undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Series 10: Chiricahua Turkey Creek, 1982, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains one subseries: Protection and Management (1982). The file documents the protection and management of the Galeyville Ranch on the site.
    - Subseries 1: Protection and Management, 1982
      - Galeyville Ranch. 1982 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Series 11: Coffeepot Mountain Macrosite, 1977-1986, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains two subseries: Ecology (1987-1988) and Protection and Management (1988). Files document the ecological resources and management of the macrosite.
    - Subseries 1: Ecology
      - Ecological Summary. 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Subseries 2: Protection and Management, 1988
      - Visit Summary. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Series 12: Eagle Creek Natural Area, 1977-1986, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains two subseries: Ecology (1982-1986) and Protection and Management (1977). Files document the ecological resources and management of the natural area.
    - Subseries 1: Ecology, 1982-1986
      - Reports-Plant and Wildlife. 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Subseries 2: Protection and Management 1977
      - Establishment Proposal. 1977 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Series 13: Empire Ranch Megasite, 1986, undated, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains two subseries: Photographs and Images (undated) and Protection and Management (1986). Files document the physical characteristics and management of the megasite.
    - Subseries 1: Photographs and Images, undated
      - General. undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Subseries 2: Protection and Management, 1986
      - ARCO Proposal and Maps. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Series 14: Escondido Falls, 1986, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains one subseries: Protection and Management (1986). The file documents the management of the Clarke tract on the site.
    - Subseries 1: Protection and Management, 1986
      - Clarke Tract. 1986 1986 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Series 15: Goodding RNA Extensions, 1987, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains two subseries: Ecology (1987) and Protection and Management (1987). Files document the ecological resources and management of the site extensions.
    - Subseries 1: Ecology, 1987
      - Ecological Summary. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Subseries 2: Protection and Management, 1987
      - Visit Summary. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Series 16: Guadalupe Canyon, 1979-1982, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains two subseries: Ecology (1981) and Protection and Management (1979-1982). Files document the ecological resources and management of the Magoffin Ranch tract of the site.
    - Subseries 1: Ecology, 1981
      - Magoffin Ranch Tract-Plants and Wildlife Spreadsheet. 1981 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Subseries 2: Protection and Management, 1979-1982
      - Magoffin Ranch Tract, Acquisition. 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Series 17: Hartwell Canyon Preserve, 1986-1989, .01 linear feet (approximately 20 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains three subseries: Ecology (1986), Photographs and Images (1989), and Protection and Management (1986). Files document the ecological resources, physical characteristics and management of the preserve.
    - Subseries 1: Ecology 1986
      - Ecological Summary and Stewardship Information,. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Subseries 2: Photographs and Images, 1989
      - General. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Subseries 3: Protection and Management, 1986
      - Project Summary. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Series 18: Hassayampa River Preserve, 1986-1994, .30 linear feet (approximately 600 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
    This series contains three subseries: Administration (1987-1994), Ecology (1986), and Protection and Management (1986-1993). Files document the fiscal administration, ecological resources, and management of the preserve.
    - Subseries 1: Administration, 1987-1994
      - Fiscal-Balance Sheet. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Fiscal-Financial Budgets and Plans. 1988-1994 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Reports-Quarterly. 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Subseries 2: Ecology, 1986
      - Ecological Summary. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Preserve Management Plan. 1988-1993 (Box 10, Folder 45-47)
      - Preserve Plans, Notes and Stewardship Summary. 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 48-49)
      - Project Package, Hassayampa River Project (Johnston). undated (Box 10, Folder 50)